[{"answer": "I was the only candidate who stood up on the debt ceiling debate and said this country shouldn't default.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "Is Jon Huntsman the real deal?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "Pre-eminence for the United States.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What is the Jon Huntsman vision for America?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "The American dream is the same.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Or should the American dream be slightly re- invented for the modern world?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "You worked in China for a couple of years and you well know that when you compare bureaucracy to China to bureaucracy in America, one of the reasons that they are marching on, good or bad, whatever your view of it, is they are not consumed with red tape over every tiny thing they do.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Why try to build something like they did the last generation?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "In an autocratic system like China, there's plenty of red tape.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "But does America have a fundamental problem business wise with the sheer volume of paperwork, red tape; legalese stuff that I believe slows down modern business?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Hard work.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "What values did he instill in you?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "We had a lot of bands but the last one, the good one, was wizard.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "What was the name of your band?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Donny and Marie did OK.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Did you see potential conflict arising?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "If you can tell me anything about Captain Beefheart, I'll give you an answer.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Now is that true?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "We've come this far.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Do you want to get your hand dirty in the grubbiness of running for high office and all that comes with it?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "They have been raised in a public environment.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Are you comfortable that they're ready?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, its early days.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Why is that and how do you change that?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Not August.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "When is the point when we should look at how you're performing and properly judge it?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I do, yes.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "You really want to get me in trouble, do you?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "I don't - well, I'll tell you what I told most people, if not everybody.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What is something that you would say to a friend over dinner?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "He appointed me and I stood up and took the appointment to serve my country.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Do you have sympathy for him in the position he found himself in where he had such an intransigent part of the Republican Party really just refusing to compromise?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, on the debt ceiling.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Where would you disagree with her?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "On gay marriage?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I am pro life.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "What is your view of abortion?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Rape, incest and life of the mother would be the exceptions that I could live with.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Do you think there are any other circumstances where you would think an abortion is acceptable?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "ON HUNTSMAN: All I have to say I don't have a lot of patience on a lot of the non-economic issues.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "When you see again intransigents by some of the particularly the tea party and of the Republican Party on this kind of thing, do you think again that it's bordering on bigotry?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Would you endorse what he said?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "You know I don't know him that well.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Do you like him?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I'm just pointing out the facts, just pointing out the facts.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "I mean you've said it in a very nice way but what you're basically doing is knifing him straight in the back, aren't you?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "You know, anyone who's going -", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "What about to a tea party candidate?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Captain Beefheart music, I assume you are talking about.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Could you entertain such idea?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I'm not going to play the name game at all.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "You wouldn't rule out Michele Bachmann?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I said whatever I say you'll have no idea what it is and after that I said, my name in Chinese and I said I'm going to become the next president of the United States.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What the hell have you just said to me?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "It's the most important relationship of the 21st century.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Of course it is unhealthy.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Because it allows them to apply a pressure that may not be good for America?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "We have no choice, Piers.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Has the time come for America to simply pull out all of its troops now from Iraq and Afghanistan and just start on concentrating on domestic issues?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "It is a counter terror effort that we are waging.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Is it acceptable for America and its national psyche and morale to pull out of two countries where a war has not been won?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Are you redefining the nature of the conflict?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "No, I'm in the keep America safe business.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Are you more in the revenge business then?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "We'll have a good debate and it will be around the issues and it will be a complete, complete approach that speaks to economic expansion and job creation where he has failed the American people miserably and where we're going to bring our strength from our background.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "If come this time next year the battle for the White House is you against Barack Obama, a man who believes he's your dear, dear friend, are you prepared to gun him down politically?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I've got what it takes to win and I've got the vision which -", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Are you politically ruthless?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Listen.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Can you be ruthless?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "of course I do.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Are you brutal at them?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Careful.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "When did you first meet John?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "It must have been disappointing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "40-year rider", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "You ride Harleys?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Something like that.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Because I think he's the greatest leader out there.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Why should he be president?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "The principles are the same, whether in Utah or whether on a national basis.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What is your great master plan?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Why would you vote against them?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "The think is there that we had a little more love to give.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What was the thinking there?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I don't know that you are ever prepared.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Are you prepared for that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I have a deep belief in God.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Where do you see the line drawn in terms of your adherence to the Mormon faith?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Well, I'd say there are 13 million Mormons around the world today.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Are you ready for this?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "You know, it just so happens that I have a daughter who actually plays somewhat.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Now, are you the only member of your family that can do this?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Don't embarrass me too bad.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "What are you going to play?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "I have a coin you can flip if you want.", "docId": "110904pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Are we agreed?", "qSentId": 662}]